Li Wen
You need to work harder.
You're a genius programmer.
Your numbers need to beat Bro Liu's.
Yes, Bro Snake.
Why are you so nervous?
I...
My numbers are bad.
I just can't cheer up.
But don't worry, Bro Snake.
I'll definitely work harder.
Good.
That's the spirit.
I'm counting on you.
Take care, Bro Snake.
You bunch of Vampires!
We will definitely root you out!
This should do it.
Old Gu, are you done yet?
Bro Snake, I...
Whenever I get nervous, I get diarrhea.
Almost done, almost done!
Stop making excuses!
You're just trying to get out of work!
I'll teach you a lesson when you're out!
What am I trying to get out of?
With a little effort, I'd be number one!
Done.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
You even monitor my shitting and pissing!
Hurry up!
Such a pain.
What a terrible case of the runs.
It stinks!
You really need to clean the bathroom.
Sir, rest assured.
Reassured, my ass!
You guys wasted such good material.
The police are watching us too closely.
Rest assured, it's much better now.
Don't let me down.
Yes.
Damn it.
Working my ass off all day,
and not a single word of praise.
Who is this Sir?
Xiao Lin.
Have we found the fraud ring's hideout?
Not yet.
They must have signal jamming equipment.
The messages we receive are intermittent.
We can only track it to a general area.
Keep searching based on this location.
Sir.
The police are on the move.
Something's wrong.
Boys,
I just closed a deal.
Everyone, keep pushing!
Let's nail these college students.
Are you with me?
What's going on?
Why did the computers crash?
Bro Snake, they crashed!
Who did this?
Who's messing around?
Get the hell out here!
Sir, we have a minor situation.
I'm handling it.
The police are here!
Quick, fall back!
The police will be here any second!
Destroy all evidence immediately!
Hurry!
Quickly destroy all hard drive data!
Fall back! Let's go!
Split up!
Don't follow me!
Go!
Old Gu!
Run, Old Gu! Hurry!
This way!
I know this way!
Hurry, hurry! Let's go!
Hurry up.
Head! Head! Head!
Nobody move!
Hands on your head!
Don't move! Get down!
Hands up! Don't move!
Hands on your head, squat down!
Everyone, gather in the courtyard.
Hair...
My hair...
Don't!
I'm fine.
Get up.
Bring them out.
Everyone, form a circle and squat down.
Captain.
Grass Snake and Bro Liu are both missing.
It's like they were tipped off.
They couldn't have gone far.
Cover all possible escape routes
and deploy your men.
Split up and pursue.
Yes, sir.
You three, come with me.
Take everyone back to the station.
Captain, why are there so few people?
They have multiple hideouts.
This is just one of them.
So,
our task ahead
remains very challenging.
You little rascal.
I knew you'd hold something back.
Let's take a break.
To save you this time,
I really took a huge risk.
I almost lost my life.
I really owe you this time.
I thought you weren't going to help me.
What exactly is your goal?
I can't tell you right now.
I've helped you so much,
yet you still won't tell me the truth.
Are you going to use me
and let the police arrest me?
There's no bad blood between us.
I won't hurt you.
I get it.
In other words,
you have a grudge against someone inside.
It's better you don't know for now.
Even though you're a scammer,
you still have a conscience.
As for extreme cases,
you never get involved.
But this isn't a long-term plan.
For Gu Ting's sake,
I advise you to stop.
I'm getting old.
I can't do anything else.
I can't just starve to death.
What if Huang Shanshan were your daughter?
What if Gu Ting were the one scammed?
What if Gu Ting were the one who died?
Could you still be this calm?
Xiao Lin.
How's the analysis of the USB drive data?
Captain.
Look here.
Your informant left a Chain Program.
The informant can only unilaterally
send us some basic messages.
But once the informant uses this channel,
it will be extremely dangerous.
Let's hope he won't need to use it.
Did we find anything else?
Come take a look.
Everyone, come here for a sec.
This fraud syndicate is very cunning.
They chose hideouts close to the border.
And these hideouts have a clear feature.
They are century-old Enclosed Buildings.
According to our investigation,
there are local Enclosed Buildings
of this kind, about 249 of them.
Most are located deep in the mountains.
The majority are abandoned and unmanaged,
making arrests extremely difficult.
That's right.
Captain.
Target number one,
codename Grass Snake.
Real name, Zhang Guangli.
Target number two,
codename Bro Liu.
Real name, Liu Zhenqiang.
The syndicate has about five departments.
First, the Data Mining Department.
It gathers information
and filters out suitable targets to scam.
The Fraud Call Department handles scams,
making a huge volume of calls
to find rare victims who will fall for it.
Third, the Live Streaming Department.
It uses porn and Suggestive live streaming
to attract male victims.
Card Farming Department provides cards.
These bank and phone cards
are all used to
disperse the funds scammed from victims.
Mules are responsible for withdrawing cash,
making the victims' money untraceable.
This is the entire syndicate structure.
We also seized
a large amount of past scam records.
In these records, we also found...
Found what?
We found Sun Yao's records.
Who are these two?
This person is likely the ring's boss.
His identity is currently a mystery.
I refer to him as Y for short.
Y's identity and profession are unknown.
This person is likely his Spy.
His identity is also a mystery right now.
The recent intelligence leak
is highly likely due to our operation
being detected by this fraud ring's Spy.
Highly likely, Captain.
This Grass Snake connects everyone.
Catch him, and we can uncover this Y.
Rest assured, we are tracking him.
Deploy more personnel.
Get a headcount of the college students.
We must promote anti-fraud in schools.
We need to race against the criminals
and race against time as well.
We absolutely cannot allow
another tragedy like Huang Shanshan's.
Yes, sir.
Get to work.
Xiao Lin.
Come with me to the hospital again
to check on Huang Shanshan.
Yes, Captain.
By the way, Captain,
we pooled this money together
to cover her medical bills and tuition.
It should be enough.
You guys...
...had the exact same idea I did.
Hello?
What?
How could this happen?
Huang Shanshan's condition has relapsed.
She's in critical condition again.